A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Lonsdale International Sporting Club - 1.1: Awards
Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art (LAICA) - 3.1: Neiman/Warhol Exhibition at LAICA 1981-82
Louganis, Greg - see swimming and diving
Louis, Allyson - see Allyson Louis Gallery
Louis, Joe - see boxing
Lowery, Nick
Nick Lowery, 1992 - 4.1: 1992, 1997
Lubel, William - 2.1: 1973
Lynch, David - 3.1: "Cig Art" Benefit Exhibitions 1996-2000
M
Maccioni, Sirio - 4.1: 2004
Mack, Barbara - see Gallery Mack
Madison Square Garden - 2.1: 1981, 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971, 1987, 1992, 1994, 1999, 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E
Madison Square Garden (silkscreen) - 4.1: 1978
Madrid, Spain - 4.1: 1960 ov
A Magic Moment, 1990 - see Orlando Magic under "baseball"
magical creatures - see animals: unicorn
Mahoney, James - 2.1: 1983, 3.1: Pebble Beach Golf 1982-1995
Mailer, Norman - 4.1: 1982
Maitland, Vic - 2.2: NFL Alumni
Make-a-Wish Foundation - 4.1: 2000
Maki, Mary Ann - 2.1: 1993, 1995, 1997
Malave, Chu Chu - see boxing
Malinowski, Mark "Scoop" - 4.1: 2000
Malletmen, 1977 etching - see polo
Manager of the Year, 1992 - see LaRussa, Tony
Mandalay Bay - 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Vargas 2002
Mandela, Nelson - 3.1: Nelson Mandela Tribute 1997
Mangione, Chuck - 4.1: 2004
Manhattan Bride Magazine - 4.1: 1999
Manhattan Concert Club - 4.1: 2004
Manhattan Magazine - 1.1: Awards, 2.1: 1989, 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Center for Print Studies, Columbia University 1995 - present, 4.1: 1984, 1990, 1997, 1998, 1999 Manila, Phillipines - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila," 1975
Mannochia, Adriano - 4.1: 1983
Mantle, Mickey - 2.1: 1998, 3.1: Mickey Mantle Paintings and Serigraphs, 1962-1999, 4.1: 1968
Mickey Mantle (or) High Ball Homer, 1962 - 3.1: Mickey Mantle Paintings and Serigraphs, 1962-1999
Mickey Mantle - Switcher, 1967 - 3.1: Mickey Mantle Paintings and Serigraphs, 1962-1999
Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company - 2.1: 1978, 2.2: Manufacturers Hanover and Chemical Bank, 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001, 3.1: Millrose Games 1986-1995, see also Chemical Bank and McCabe, Charles
marathon - see running
March of Dimes - 2.1: 1981, 1982, 3.1: March of Dimes' Gourmet Gala 1985, 4.1: 1974, 1981, 1983, 1985
Mardi Gras - 3.1: Rex Proclamation Mardi Gras Poster Painting 2002, 4.1: 1987, 2001
Marichal, Juan, Juan Marichal - 4.1: 1995
marionette - 4.1: 1981, 1984
Marketing Communications Magazine - 2.1: 1980, 4.1: 1980
Marlin!, 1977 serigraph - 2.1: 1977, 4.1: 1977 ov
Marmel, David - 3.1: Beauty Pageants 1980-84, 3.1: Victor Awards 1981-85
Marquis Who's Who - 1.1: Who's Who
Marshall Field & Company - 3.1: Fashion Illustration for Marshall Field 1957-59 (Oversize only)
Marshall, Leonard, Leonard Marshall, 1991 - 4.1: 1991, 1992
Martin, Billy, Billy Martin, 1990 drawing - 2.1: 1990
Marx, Groucho - 3.1: Charlotte Chandler 1978-84
Maser Galleries, Maser Fine Arts - 2.1: 1988, 1989, 3.1: 1983 U.S. Open, Oakmont, 1983
Mashburn, Jamal - 4.1: 1990
mask auction - 4.1: 1988
Mason, Jackie - 4.1: 1994
Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - 1.1: Awards: Citations, 4.1: 1982
matador - see bullfights
Mathis, Buster - see boxing
Matsui, 2004 - 3.1: Special Olympics Nagano Japan 2005
The Maulers 1993 lithograph - see boxing
Max, Peter - 4.1: 1994, 1995, 1980s and 1990s (mentioned throughout)
Mayo Clinic - 2.1: 1983
mayoral debate - 4.1: 1989, see also politics
Mays, Willie - 4.1: 1992, Wille Mays - 2.2: 1978, 4.1: 1979, 1982, 2001
Mazeroski, Bill, Bill Mazeroski - 4.1: 1973
Mazzilli, Lee, Lee Mazzilli, 1979 - 2.1: 1979, 2001 4.1: 2001, Lee Mazzilli Celebrity Golf and Tennis Classic - 2.1: 2001, 4.1: 1992, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 2001
McCabe, Charles - 2.1: 1995, 2.2: Manufacturers Hanover and Chemical Bank, 3.1: Iona College Trustee Awards Dinner Dances 1984-95, 4.1: 1987, 1997, see also Chemical Bank
McCormack, Mark H. - see The Wonderful World of Professional Golf by Mark H. McCormack under golf
McDonald, Kitt - 4.1: 1986
McDougal, Little & Company - 2.1: 1985
McEneaney, Eamon - 4.1: 2001, 2005
McEnroe, John - see tennis
McFagan, Helen - 2.1: 1993
McGirt, James "Buddy" - see boxing
McGraw-Hill Publishers - 2.1: 1999
McGuire, Al - 4.1: 1980
McGwire, Mark, Mark McGwire, 1998 - 3.1: Mark McGwire 1998-99, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002, 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation, 1998-2002
McHale, Kevin - see Johnson, Earvin "Magic": Magic
McNeely, Peter - 4.1: 1995
McNichol, Kristy - 2.1: 1980
Mead, Margaret, Margaret Mead, 1972 drawing - 4.1: 1977 ov
Meigs, Kris - 2.1: 1981
Melville, Herman - 3.2. Moby Dick, 1975, The Artist's Limited Edition
Memphis Blues Ball - 4.1: 1998
Men, Boats, and the Sea, 1955 - 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Instructors Exhibition 1955
menus - 4.1: 1977, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1997, 1999, see also food, restaurants
medical - see The Open Heart, 1982
Mercantile Bank, Chicago and Hammond, IN - 3.1: Mercantile Bank Murals 1966
merchandise - see promotions, product and service, and collectible merchandise
Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago - 2.2: Merrill Chase Galleries 1974-89, 4.1: 1973, 1976, 1980, 1981, 1982 see exhibitions
Metropolitan Museum of Art - 2.1: 1981
Metropolitan Opera - see opera
Mexico - 3.1: Caliente Race Track Exhibition and Painting 1989
MGM Grand Gallery - 4.1: 1999
Miami Sound Machine - see Estefan, Emilio and Gloria
Michael Zabrin Fine Art - 2.1: 1989
Michaels, Walt - 2.1: 1980, see also football: New York Jets
Midwest Museum of American Art - 4.1: 1979, 1989, see also exhibitions
Miles, Sylvia - 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo), 4.1: 1991
Minelli, Liza - 3.1: Frank Sinatra at Royal Albert Hall 1989
miniatures - 4.1: 1983
Minnesota Historical Society - 2.1: 1994
Minnesota Museum of Art - 3.1: St. Paul Bicentennial Painting 1975-76, see also exhibitions
Minotaur Galleries - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984-1994, 4.1: 1986, see also exhibitions
John Miles Bonded Travel Agency - 4.1: undated
military - 1.1: Military Service
Million Dollar Strike, 1982 - see bowling
Millionaire Magazine - 3.1: Joe DiMaggio 1998-99
Millrose Games - 3.1: Millrose Games 1986-1995
Milt Gross Fund - 2.1: 2000, 4.1: 2001
Minuteman, 1987 - 3.1: U.S. Savings Bonds Campaign 1987-88
Mirrer, Louise - IC: A Sociological Study of the Artist LeRoy Neiman, and 1000 Neiman Collectors by David Halle and Louis Mirrer, 1990
Mitchell, Mayer - 2.1: 1972, 1976, 1977, 1987
The Mixologist, 1959 - see bars
Moby Dick, 1975 - 2.1: 1993, 3.2.2
models - 3.1: Beauty Pageants 1980-84, see also Eve Models, Inc., search for individual models by name
Monaco - see also Bal de la Mer, Monte Carlo, auto racing, French Riviera
Monaco Rendezvous, 1994 - 3.1: Monaco Trip 1994
Monmouth Park Charity Ball - 2.1: Charities (all dates, 1980s, 1990s)
Monroe, Earl, Earl "The Pearl" Monroe, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Montana, Joe, Joe Montana, 1982 - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91, 4.1: 1982, 1990
Montanez, Willie - 4.1: 1979
Monte Carlo, Monaco - 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E, see auto racing, Monaco
Monte Carlo, 1994 - 4.1: 1999
Monte Carlo Chase, 1988 - 2.2: Neiman -Marcus 1983-88, 3.1: Steiner & Young Galleries Solo Exhibition 1989, 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd.
Japanese Edition - 2.2: Joe Hideo Morita 1988-90
Moore, Wayland - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries
Moorer, Michael - 4.1: 1994
Morbelli, Jean - 2.1: 1988
Moreno, Linda "Eva" - 2.2: Linda Moreno
Morgan, Joe, Joe Morgan, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Morita, Joe Hideo - 2.2: Joe Hideo Morita 1988-90
Morley, Malcolm - 4.1: 1984
Morocco - 4.2: Playboy 1970, see Appendix E
Morrel Wines - 4.1: 1984
Morris, Gary and Elizabeth - 2.1: 1996, 3.1: Iroquois Steeplechase, Nashville, TN, 1993
Morrison, Tommy - see boxing
Morton's of Chicago - see restaurants
Moscow - 3.1: Goodwill Games Moscow 1986, 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries 1987, V: 1960s
Tretyakov Museum - 3.1: Tretyakov Museum Solo Exhibition, Moscow 1988
Mosley, Shane - see boxing
Mount Pleasant Animal Shelter - 4.1: 2000
Mozartfest - 4.1: 1998
Mthembu, Nomusa - 2.1: 1992
Mulloy, Gardner - 4.1: 1998
multiple sclerosis - see National Multiple Sclerosis Society, or Race to Erase MS
Munich, Germany - see Olympic Games
Municipal Art League of Chicago Award - 1.1: Awards
Munson, Thurman - 3.1: Thurman Munson and Thurman Munson Awards 1977-2002, Thurman Munson, 1976 - 3.1: Thurman Munson and Thurman Munson Awards 1977-2002
murals - 3.1: Mercantile Bank Murals 1966, 3.1: Sportsman's Park Mural 1976, 3.1: Elayne Galleries Solo Exhibition and P.J. Clarkes, Minneapolis, 1978, 3.1: Stadium Tennis Billboard 1981, 3.1: "The Playboy Collection," Dyansen Gallery Traveling Exhibition 1989-90
Murphy Brown - see Warner Brothers Television in Appendix A
Murphy, Dale - 2.1: 1993, 1995, 4.1: 1993
Murphy, Libby - 2.2: Libby Murphy 1992-1998, 3.1: Iroquois Steeplechase, Nashville, TN, 1993
Murphy, Father Terrence - 4.1: 2004
Muscle Builder & Power Magazine - 4.1: 1977
Muscular Dystrophy Associations of America - 4.1: 1971, 1987
Lifetime Achievement Award - 1.1: Awards
Museo de Bellas Artes, Caracas - 2.1: 1972 see also exhibitions
Museum of the City of New York, Theater Collection - 3.1: Showstoppers Group Exhibition, MCNY 1983
music - 4.1: 1970, 1981, 1983, 1992, see also Gibson Guitars
blues - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997 -2004, see Paul, Les
classical - 4.1: 1964, 1965, 1998, see also Bernstein, Leonard; Eaton, Roy; Fox, Virgil; Grady, John; Raphael, James
Arkansas Symphony Orchestra - 3.1: Arkansas Symphony Orchestra and Arkansas Wild Ducks, 1984
Desert Symphony - 4.1: 1997
Oakland Symphony - 2.1: 1985
The Organ at St. Paul the Apostle, 1965 - 4.1: 1965, 1967
Symphantasy - 3.1: Symphantasy 1988
Symphony for United Nations, 1991 - 2.1: 1991, 4.1: 1991
country - 4.1: 1994, see Tennessee
jazz - see jazz
opera - see opera
popular - 3.1: Fifth Dimension Album Art 1970-82, 3.1: Billboard Magazine First Annual Billie Awards 1993, 4.1: 1993, see The Beatles; Bennet, Tony; Blues Ball; Davis, Sammy; Iglesias, Julio; Jackson, Michael; Lennon, John; Paul, Les; Sinatra, Frank
musicals - see Times Square, 2001
Angels on Horseback - 4.1: undated 1980s
Golden Boy - 4.1: 1964
My Fair Lady - 3.1: Showstoppers Group Exhibition, MCNY 1983, 4.1: 1983
Oh! Calcutta - 4.1: 1967
Porgy and Bess - 3.1: Showstoppers Group Exhibition, MCNY 1983, 4.1: 1983
West Side Story - 3.1: Showstoppers Group Exhibition, MCNY 1983, 4.1: 1983
Mustang Ranch - 3.1: Mustang Ranch Brothel 1989
Myasthenia Gravis Foundation - 4.1: 1978
Myers, Farlan - 2.1: 1986
Mystic Seaport, CT - 3.2. Moby Dick, 1975, The Artist's Limited Edition
Mystic Rock, 1995 - 4.1: 1997
N
NAMTA - 4.1: 1984
NBC - see television
NECO (National Ethnic Coalition of Organizations) - 1.1: Awards, Citations and Miscellaneous Prizes
Nabisco - see promotions
Nahan, Kenneth - 4.1: undated
Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame - see basketball
Namath, Joe - 3.1: New York Jets 1966-, 4.1: 1968, 1972, 1973, 1982
Napoleon at Waterloo, 1988 serigraph - 4.1: 1988
Nash, Beau - 3.1: The Ambassadors, 1960s
The Nation Magazine - 2.1: 1998, 4.1: 1998
National Art Museum of Sport (NAMOS) - 2.1: 1972, 1979, 4.1: 1980, 2003 see also exhibitions
National Arts Club - 4.1: 1994
National Baseball Hall of Fame and Museum, Cooperstown, NY - see baseball
National Bowling Hall of Fame and Museum - see bowling - Million Dollar Strike, 1982
National Cowboy Hall of Fame - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: National Cowboy Hall of Fame 1985
National Fitness Classic - 4.1: 1982, 1983
National Multiple Sclerosis Society - 4.1: 1969, 1976, 1980, 1988
National Sports Collectors Convention - 4.1: 1992 ov.
NBA - see basketball
negative press - 2.1: 1980, 4.1: 1978, 1979, 1981, 1983
Neiman, Earl - 1.1: Family (Neiman Studio Archive only)
Neiman, Janet - 1.1: Family, 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Instructors Exhibition 1955, 4.1: 1985
Neiman News - 3.1: Neiman News 1977-1985
Neiman-Marcus - 2.2: Neiman-Marcus 1983-88, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, 4.1: 1983, 1984
Neiman, Robert B - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries
"Neiman's Cuba" film project - 2.1: 1979, 1982
Neiman's Restaurant & Lounge - see restaurants and bars
Nepal - 2.1: 1982
Nevada County Arts Council - 4.1: 1982
New Jersey State Opera Ball - see opera
New Milford Hospital - 4.1: 1991
New Orleans, Louisiana - 2.1: 1993, 1997, 1998, see also Hanson Art Galleries and Mardi Gras
New School for Social Research, NY - 4.1: 1978
New Times Magazine - 2.1: 1978
New Year's Eve, 1997 - 4.1: 1997 and ov
New York City Marathon - see running
New York Friars Club - 4.1: 1999
New York Giants - see Football
New York and Los Angeles: Politics, Society, and Culture by David Halle - 3.1: UCLA LeRoy Neiman Center for the Study of American Society and Culture, 1998-present
New York Public Library - 4.1: 2002
New York State Governor's Arts Awards - 4.1: 2000
New York Times Magazine - 4.1: 1971
The New Yorker Magazine - 4.1: 1994, 1999
Newman, Eric - V: 1975
Newman, Paul - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993, see also The Hustler
Newport Jazz Festival - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Newsweek Magazine - 4.1: 1972, 1992
Newton, Wayne - 4.1: 1988
NFL - see football
NHL - see hockey
Niarchos, Stavros
Stavros Niarchos, 1969 drawing - 4.1: 1969 ov.
Nicholson, Jack - 3.1: Tyson vs. Spinks 1988
Nicklaus, Jack - see golf
Nitschke, Ray - 4.1: 1988
Noah, Yannick - see tennis
Nob Hill, 1986 serigraph - 3.1: Nob Hill and Bowles Hopkins Gallery 1986
Norman, Greg, Greg Norman - 2.1: 1990
North Shore Art League - 1.1: Education and Teaching, Miscellaneous, undated
North Shore Child and Family Guidance Association - 4.1: 1986, 1987
Northern Indiana Art Association - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989
Northwest Orient Magazine - 4.1: 1986
Northwest Paper Company - 3.1: 1972 Olympics
Northwestern University - 2.1: 1978
Norton, Ken - see boxing
Norton Herrick Fine Arts Group - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Website 1997-present
Norway - 2.1: 1988
Notre Dame - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002
Nureyev, Rudolph - see ballet
O
Ocean Club, Atlantic City - see promotions
Everett Oehlschlaeger Galleries, Chicago - 2.1: 1960s, 4.1: 1973, 1975
Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Sarasota, FL - 3.1: "American Masters of the 40s, 50s, and 60s", Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, 1985
Oesch, Claire - 2.1: 1994, 1995
Oh! Calcutta - see musicals
Oklahoma - see Bennett, Chef John, and baseball: Oklahoma Redhawks (minor league)
Olin Corporation - see promotions
Olympic Games - 4.1: 1984
1972 Olympics, Munich - 3.1: 1972 Olympics, Munich, 4.1: 1987
1976 Olympics, Montreal - 3.1: 1976 Olympics, Montreal, 4.1: 1987
Games of the XXI Olympiad, 1976 - 3.1: Volvo Masters Painting 1983
Olympic Boxers, 1976 - 3.1: 1976 Olympics, Montreal
1980 Winter Olympics, Lake Placid - 3.1: Winter Olympics, Lake Placid 1980
Olympic Figure Skating, 1978 - 3.1: Winter Olympics, Lake Placid 1980
Winter Olympic Skiing, 1980 - 3.1: Winter Olympics, Lake Placid 1980
1984 Winter Olympics, Sarajevo - 3.1: Sarajevo Winter Olympics 1984
1984 Olympics, Los Angeles - 3.1: 1984 Olympics, Los Angeles, 3.1: Center Art Galleries Exhibition, Hawaii, 1985
American Gold, 1984 - 4.1: 1984
Opening Ceremonies - XXIII Olympiad 1984, 1984 - 4.1: 1984
1988 Olympics, Seoul - 2.1: 1988, 4.1: 1988
1988 Winter Olympics, Calgary - 2.1: 1986, 1987
1992 Olympics, Barcelona - 2.1: 1989
1994 Winter Olympics, Lillehammer - 3.1: 1994 Winter Olympics, Lillehammer
1996 Olympics, Atlanta - 3.1: Atlanta Olympics 1996
2000 Olympics - 3.1: 2000 Olympics
2004 Olympic bid - 2.1: 1989
boxing - 3.1: 2000 Olympics
Olympic Boxing - 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Olympics of Tomorrow - 4.1: 1978
U.S. Olympic Fight Night - 2.1: 1996, 4.1: 1996
Spring Serenade 2004 - 4.1: 2004
OMTI (Opera Music Theatre International) LeRoy Neiman Recital Hall - see opera
On Safari - see LeRoy Neiman On Safari
Onassis, Aristotle, Aristotle Onassis, 1969 drawing - 4.1: 1969 ov.
O'Neal, Shaquille, Shaquille O'Neal, 2000 - 3.1: Shaquille O'Neal, 2000
Ono, Yoko - 2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1984 -98, 3.1: John Lennon Etching 1990
The Open Heart, 1982 - 3.1: The Open Heart, 1982
opera - see also Le Grand Escalier de l'Opera, 1969
Amahl and the Night Visitors, 1978 - 4.1: 1978
Ballroom Scene from 'La Traviata', 1980 - New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings 1979-83
Falstaff, opera by Verdi - 2.1: 2002, 3.1: Falstaff Opera 1993, 4.1: 2002
Hines, Jerome and Lucia - 3.1: New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings 1979-83, 3.1: OMTI LeRoy Neiman Opera Lab Theater 1995
Jerome Hines as Boris Godunov, 1988 drawing - 4.1: 1988
Metropolitan Opera - 2.1: 2002
Metropolitan Opera - 2.1: 1980, 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s
New Jersey State Opera Ball - 3.1: New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings 1979-83
A Night at the Opera, drawing - 4.1: 1989
Opera Music Theater International - 3.1: OMTI LeRoy Neiman Opera Lab Theater 1995, 4.1: 1989, 4.1: 1991
Pagliacci, 1982 - 3.1: New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings 1979-83
The Three Tenors, 1996 serigraph release - 3.1: The Three Tenors, 1996
organists - see Fox, Virgil; Grady, John
Original Print Collectors' Group, Ltd. - 4.1: 1989
Orr, Bobby - 4.1: 1977
Orr for the Defense, 1992 - 2.1: 1992, 3.1: Orr for the Defense, 1992, 4.1: 1992
Oslo, Norway - 2.1: 1988
Our Lady of Mercy Medical Center - 4.1: 1997
Outrigger Canoe Race, 1976 - 4.1: undated 1970s
Owens, Jesse - see track and field
Ox-Bow, the Summer School of Painting, Saugatuck, Michigan - 1.1: Education and Teaching, 2.1: 2001, 3.1: Ox -Bow 1998
Oxendine, Kit - 1.1: Lynn Quayle, V:1990s
P
P.J. Clarke's, New York - see restaurants
P.O.V. Magazine - 4.1: 1998
Pacino, Al - 2.1: 1983
Paige, Satchel - 3.1: Economic Opportunity Atlanta 1968 ov.
Pallack, Rick - 2.1: 1996, 1999, 4.1: 1996
Palm Beach, Florida - V: 1970s
Palm Springs, California - 3.1: Palm Springs Commemorative Coin, 1987-88
Palmer, Arnold - see golf
Palmer, Jim, Jim Palmer, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Papp, L. Roy - 3.1: L. Roy Papp, 1980
Pappas, Thomas, Thomas A. Pappas, 1969 drawing - 4.1: 1969 ov.
Paris, France - 3.1: "Un Americain à Paris," Solo Exhibition, Galerie Marcel Bernheim, Paris 1993, 4.1: 1963
Paris, 1989 - 3.1: Kentucky Derby 1995-97
Paris Match Magazine - 4.1: 1961, 1962
Parker, Charlie - see jazz
Parks Council - 4.1: 1976
Paschke, Ed - 2.1: 1988, 1990, 2.3
Pastorini, Dan - 2.1: 1989
Patrician Galleries - 2.1: 1987
Patrick, John 'Malt Liquor' - 3.1: Economic Opportunity Atlanta 1968 ov.
Paterson Museum, Paterson, NJ - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1996
Patterson, Floyd - see boxing
Paul, Les - 2.1: 1997
Pavarotti, Luciano - 3.1: The Three Tenors, 1996
PAWS/LA - 2.1: 1999, 4.1: 2000
Payne, Marcus - 2.1: 1982
Pazienza, Vinny - 4.1: 1995
Peaches and Pits Awards - 4.1: 1987, 2000
Pebble Beach - see golf
Pele - see soccer
Pelkey, Joe - 2.1: 1990, 1993, 2.2: Joe Pelkey, Editions Limited
pendant - VII: Painting pendants, undated
Peninsula Sports Club - 4.1: 1973
Penn, Esther - 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo), 4.1: 1999
Penske, Roger - see auto racing
Penthouse Magazine - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries
Percival Galleries - 2.1: 1979, see also exhibitions
perfume - see promotions
Peri-Renneth Gallery, Southampton - 2.1: 1988, 4.1: 1984
Perkins, Carl - 2.2: Libby Murphy
Perry, Gaylord - 3.1: Gaylord Perry's 300th Win file
Perse, Joanne - 4.1: 1986
PESO - 3.2: LeRoy Neiman Art and Lifestyle 1974
Phelps, Digger - 2.1: 1990
Philadelphia Sports Writers Association - 4.1: 2000
Phillipines - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila," 1975
pianists - see Eaton, Roy; Raphael, James, see also music: classical
Piazza, Mike, Mike Piazza, 1999 - 3.1: Mike Piazza 1999
Piazza San Marco, 1990 - 3.1: Piazza San Marco, 1990, 2001-2002
Pierrot, drawing - 4.1: 1975
Pierrot, lithograph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Pierrot the Juggler, lithograph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
The Pitman Company - 4.1: 1984
Pizza Hut - 2.1: 1991, 4.1: 1992 ov
La Plage de Deauville, 1990 - 2.1: 1990
plates, collectible - see Royal Doulton
Plate Collector Magazine - 2.1: 1980
The Playboy, painting - 4.1: 1990
Playboy Enterprises International - 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s, 4.1: 2001 art auction - 4.1: 1989, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 2000s
New York Playboy Club - 4.2: Playboy 1965, see Appendix E
Playboy Art Collection - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989, 4.1: 1975, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 2000s
Playboy Jazz Festival, 1980 - 4.1: 1980
Playboy Magazine and Man at His Leisure - see Appendix E, 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s, 3.1: 1984 Olympics, Los Angeles, 4.1: 1959, 1966, 1999, 4.2: Playboy Magazine, V: Playboy Clubs 1961-63
Femlin - 2.1: 1985, 4.1: 1995, 2001, 4.2: Playboy Magazine, 4.2: Playboy - Femlin Paraphernalia
Playboy of Brazil - 2.1: 1985
Special Editions, Ltd. - 4.1: 1992
Players Hotel, New Orleans - 2.1: 1984
The Plaza Hotel, New York - 4.2: Playboy 1965, see Appendix E
The Plaza Square, 1985 - 4.1: 1985, 1986
tapestry - 2.1: 1990
Poland - 2.1: 1976, 1987
Plunkett, Sherman - 4.1: 1967
Police Athletic League - 2.1: 1981
politics - 3.1: Bill Bradley 1978-2000, 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980, 3.1: Peter Dawkins Poster 1988, 3.1: Rudy Giulianni and Commission on Cultural Affairs 1994-2001, 3.1: Nelson Mandela Tribute 1997, 4.1: 1960, 1968, 1988, 1989, 1992, see also Thurmond, Strom, and The White House
Pollock, Jackson - 4.1: 1984
polo - 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1988
Attack, 1965 - 4.1: 1967
elephant polo - 2.1: 1982
H.R.H. Prince Charles, 1982 - 4.1: 1985
Malletmen, 1977 etching - 3.1: Malletmen Certificate 1977
Polo Player, 1963 - 4.1: 1963
Polo Players, 1964 - 4.1: 1991
Polo Lounge, 1988 - 2.1: 1989, 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s, 3.1: Polo Lounge debut at Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Bev Hills 1989, 4.1: 1990, 1995, 1996, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002
The Pope Flies Over New York, detail - 4.1: 1981
Pope, Kerig - 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s
Porgy and Bess - see musicals
Porter, David - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Portola Valley Classic Equestrian Festival - 4.1: 1999
Portrait of the Lion, 2002 - see animals
portraits - 3.1: "Portraits of Our Times 1946-96" Solo Exhibition and Catalog, Bowles/Sorokko/Yarger Galleries, 1996
of LeRoy Neiman, by other artists - 2.1: 1978, 3.1: Elayne Galleries Solo Exhibition and P.J. Clarkes, Minneapolis, 1978, 4.1: 1986 ov
by LeRoy Neiman - search by name of subject
Posner Gallery - 2.1: 1989
posters - 3.2. Posters, 1980, Harry N. Abrams, 4.1: 1981, 1993
Posters, 1980 - 3.2. Posters, 1980, Harry N. Abrams, 3.2 ov.
Pratt Institute, New York - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Cuba" Solo Exhibition, Pratt Institute, New York, 2003
Preakness Stakes - see horse racing
Prentice - Hall Publishers - 2.1: 1978
President of the United States - see politics, or search by name of President (Carter, Reagan, Bush, Clinton)
President's Council on Physical Fitness and Sports - 2.1: 1990, 4.1: 1982, 1983
Presley, Elvis - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004, 4.2: Playboy 1978 (July)
price lists - IID: Price Lists
Prince Charles, 1984 - 4.1: 1984
prints - 3.1: The Etchings of LeRoy Neiman, 1976 booklet (ov), see also The Prints of LeRoy Neiman below
The Prints of LeRoy Neiman, 1980 - 3.2. The Prints of LeRoy Neiman, 1980, Knoedler Publishing
The Prints of LeRoy Neiman 1980-1990, 1991 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Solo Exhibition, Atlantic City 1992, 3.2. The Prints of LeRoy Neiman, 1980-1990, 1991
The Prints of LeRoy Neiman 1991-2000, 2001 - 3.2.14
Professional Picture Framers Association - 4.1: 1984
promotions, product and service, and collectible merchandise
AMF Incorporated (soccer equipment) - 3.1: AMF Soccer Equipment Promotion 1979
Absolut Vodka
Absolut Neiman, 1970 - 3.1: Absolut Vodka ad 1991, 4.2: Bartender Magazine
Alexander Hotel, Miami Beach, 1985 commercial - 3.1: Alexander Hotel Promotion 1985
Anheuser-Busch - 3.1: Duran vs. Leonard 1989
Clydesdales, 1979 - 4.1: 1979, 1983
World Cup Soccer poster 1990 - 3.1: Anheuser Busch World Cup Soccer poster 1990
Arrow shirts, The Arrow Man, 1986 - 3.1: Arrow shirts promotion 1986
Atomic skis - 2.2: Joe Hideo Morita 1988-90
Burger King - 3.1: Burger King Promotion 1976
Canadian Club Whiskey - 4.1: 1979